Uh, it's pride month. I recently learned
that the queer community added on to the
acronym. There's more.
There's an addition. There's more.
They added \slash} 2S. Stands for
two-spirit. Basically means if you feel
like you embody the spirit of both male
and female. Now there's a space for you.
Originated with indigenous tribes and I
think that's kind of dope. I don't know
if those spirits are [\h__\h] That's not
my business. I'm just
>> [laughter]
>> I'm just trying to pass information to
the people.
And people complain and I get it to an
extent, you know?
LGBTQIA+
2S is long.
>> [laughter]
>> But LGBTQIA+
2S
is a strong ass password.
>> [laughter]
>> That's military grade encryption right
there.
You can't deny that and I don't care
where you align.
And it's better than the passwords I
use, which is obviously uh p u dollar
sign dollar sign y
>> [laughter]
>> 24/7, which is pretty much all I'm
about, but
I'm just trying to log in my Wells Fargo
account, dog.
They don't need all that information.
>> [laughter]
>> If you watch enough stand-up, you start
picking up on the trends. How comics
talk a lot about dating, you know, and
and how it's how it's hard. Which it is.
Dating is hard. Dating is hard. Dating
is hard for me, too, you know, cuz I'm
married.
>> [laughter]
>> It's hard for me, too. I want to be out
there like the rest of the boys
on the apps, lying about my height.
I'm joking, but it is hard in your 30s
cuz, you know, once you into your 30s,
they want you to stop lying.
Um they want you to be honest about who
you are and what you represent, but they
also want you to be confident.
And sometimes honesty and confidence
don't necessarily align, depending on
your situation. Like this girl once told
me, she was like, "Um, a real man knows
how to fix a car." And I was just like,
"Uh, [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> I don't have a car."
So, what?
>> [laughter]
>> But it's good to be honest, you know?
Like one time I was hanging out with
this girl.
Um, I had rollerbladed to her house.
>> [laughter]
>> And
and uh and I was in her kitchen, you
know, barefoot cuz she made me take the
skates off.
And um and I and I noticed that she had
two pieces of bread left, but not two
end pieces. She had an end piece and
then a regular piece, which meant that
she eats her bread in order.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> And I I I had to leave.
I don't have that kind of structure in
my life.
>> [laughter]
>> And the bread was still sealed with that
little blue twist tie.
She went through an entire loaf of bread
without losing that little blue twist
tie. That's a level of [\h__\h]
responsibility that I'm not on
>> [laughter]
>> at all. Two pieces into a loaf of bread,
I lose that twist tie. So, then I got to
tie my bag into a knot. And then when I
come back later for a sandwich, I have
to cut the bag open
because I tied the knot too tight. And I
only wanted one sandwich, but now I got
to make three to give myself extra bag
space to tie another knot. So, it's
like, let's be honest, I'm not going to
be able to meet her needs.
>> [laughter]
>> I skated home.
Back to my wife.
I got time for this.
>> [laughter]
>> Glad y'all laughed at that joke. That
means a lot to me, makes me feel good
because I do that joke in San Francisco
and I'll be honest people they don't
like it. They get uncomfortable.
They get uncomfortable. They tense up,
you know, cuz they're gluten-free.
They can't process it.
Just one of them things, dog.
Getting older, I'm at a weird age.
I'm at a age where I realize I realize I
don't want kids.
You know?
Yeah.
I mean I have them but I don't want
them.
>> [laughter]
>> So I'm just navigating that every day.
Send help.
I never wanted kids cuz I got a big
family, big dysfunctional family. I got
16 nieces and nephews. Yeah, one brother
and sister.
>> [laughter]
>> My brother has seven kids including two
kids. They're the same age. They're not
twins. My sister
has nine kids including a set of
triplets. It's three kids. You guys know
that.
It's three kids but there's two fathers.
There's two different dudes between the
three. One guy fathers two of the
triplets and another guy fathers the
other.
Wow, how the [\h__\h] is that possible?
[\h__\h] I don't know.
But probably the same way you find an
onion ring in your french fries.
>> [laughter]
>> No one knows.
Still eat that [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> I never wanted kids. I hate my nephews.
Um
I went up to the Bay Area to celebrate
my 35th birthday and one of my nephews
asked me if he could have my laptop when
I die.
>> [laughter]
>> And And was like, "Bro, it's my
birthday." But also, do you know how
computers work? Do you know how death
works? Like I plan on being here a
minute. You know what I'm saying? I'm a
35-year-old fit nonsmoker, non-rapper.
Um
>> [laughter]
>> I live in a up-and-coming neighborhood
across the street from a Whole Foods. I
plan on being here
>> [laughter]
>> a minute. You don't think that I'mma
outlive a 2016 refurbished MacBook Pro
with no space bar?
>> [laughter]
>> The [\h__\h] space bar is broken. You
think that I'mma die before I spill
another latte on that [\h__\h]
Which would be partly my fault, but also
the fault of the Starbucks in San
Francisco on 16th and Montgomery Street
for having wobbly ass tables when I
stood up too fast to take a [\h__\h] because
coffee strikes without warning.
>> [laughter]
>> But my nephew's a hood kid, so all he
knows is like hood-related death. He's
like, "But Uncle, what if you get shot?"
And I was like, "Why are you so excited?
But you're right. I could get shot. I
could. But I just exited that 15-to-34
age range where homicide is the leading
cause of death amongst black males. You,
sir, just entered it. So
uh let me get your Xbox."
Seems fair.
I got two kids. My uh my kids are
biracial. Uh I am black, person of
color.
Their mother's a person who reflects and
scatters all visible wavelengths of
light.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> She's She's white. She's white. If you
Yeah, I'm
It's kind of confusing. I get it. I
know. Reflects and scatters all visible.
>> [laughter]
>> People be thinking I procreated with a
Care Bear.
My son's five. Hardest part about that
is because he's five, he has
five-year-old problems, and it's my job
to take his five-year-old problems
seriously. And sometimes it's hard.
Sometimes it's hard. Like he kind of got
bullied for the first time. It wasn't
anything significant, but he was at
school in the bathroom using a urinal,
and a first-grader came in and told my
son to pick his penis up and then ran
out.
>> [laughter]
>> And that was hard for me because now I
got to sit down and I got to have a
conversation with my son, and I have to
engage with him, and I have to look him
in the eyes, and I have to pretend like
"Pick your penis up" wasn't the funniest
[\h__\h] I ever heard in my life.
And that is my responsibility as a
parent.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm I'm I'm trying not to laugh. I'm
like I'm like
Did you tell a teacher? And he was like,
"No. I I I just looked on the ground for
my penis."
And I was like, "Hell yeah, man. Logic.
Hell yeah." Cuz the last thing you want
is to be at the sink and your penis is
still at the urinal. Now you got
sanitation issues. You got much bigger
problems. Pick your penis up. What does
that even mean?
What does that even mean? I have no idea
what that means, but I have been using
that [\h__\h] every day.
>> [laughter]
>> It's funny.
It's funny. Last week I was supposed to
go get drinks with the homie and catch
up, and he called me up. He was like,
"Hey, dog. We got to take a rain check,
bro. I got a little situation with the
wife." I was like, "Situation with the
wife, my [\h__\h] PICK YOUR PENIS UP."
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT? SITUATION?
Pick it up, rinse it off, put it back.
Dry it off.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know what that means.
But the phone goes silent. And all I
heard was,
"You right."
"I do need to pick my penis up. You know
what? I'm on my way."
So he came through.
We got that drink.
And he's been crashing on my couch ever
since.
That's how life goes. So I'm a father,
and the dopest part about being a parent
is like being able to give my son the
childhood that I never had because you
know cuz my dad wasn't really around
like that. So it's cool to just see him
have like a normal childhood and I can
just tell early on the way that he
interacts and the way that he responds
to things and I was like, "Damn, dog.
Like your life is going to be so much
better."
Like the other night I asked him what he
wanted to be when he grows up and he
said um he said
he said he said a flower.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, [\h__\h] ass [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
[cheering]
>> I'm not raising no god damn flowers in
my house. Pick your god DAMN PENIS UP.
>> [laughter and cheering]
[applause]
>> SO SOMEBODY WAS LIKE, "MAYBE YOUR SON
WOULDN'T WANT to be a flower if you stop
dressing like a hipster Vietnamese
fisherman."
>> [laughter]
>> Uh I take a lot of pride.
Travel a lot doing stand-up. I take a
lot of pride in having good travel
etiquette. Just knowing my role on the
flight.
Like if I'm in the window seat, then I'm
going to be getting some work done. You
know, I'll be staring out the window,
taking a nap. If I'm in the aisle seat,
then I'm going to be getting up a lot,
stretching my legs, moving around. If
I'm in the middle seat, then I [\h__\h] up
somewhere along the way.
This was not the plan. Recently I took a
flight from San Francisco to Los
Angeles, short flight, made a crucial
error. I had to pee. Had to pee on a
short flight. And it's already rude to
excuse yourself on a short flight cuz
it's like, you know, we're adults.
Control your bladder.
>> [laughter]
>> But it's worse to excuse yourself after
drinks have been served and snacks have
been served because people got their
phones out and they're comfortable,
they're watching their shows and I tried
to hold it. I truly did. I tried to hold
it, you got to believe me. I did. But
I'm in the window seat and I had to go.
So I excused myself to the middle seat,
forcing him to gather up all of his
drinks and his snacks and his phone and
lift his tray table up. But when he
tried to get up, he got yanked back down
by the seatbelt because he forgot to
unbuckle his seatbelt. So now he's just
sitting there with his hands full and
his seatbelt still buckled.
>> [laughter]
>> And he and I
exchange eyes.
>> [laughter]
>> I
I
unbuckled another man's seatbelt.
>> [laughter]
>> And I'll never fly Delta Airlines again.
>> I don't like the way they move. I don't
like their clientele.
>> [laughter]
>> When I got home, I told my lady what
happened and her response was um you
know, you could have just held his
drinks.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
[cheering and applause]
[music]